I didn't choose you
just to shake him off
Because I chose the wrong person
in my past life
In this life I want to
make the right choice
Getting married is a big deal
It's not too late to back out
Do you even know me
Not yet
We can get to know each other later
Once we get married
you won't just be using me as a stand-in
I will take it seriously
Me too
Where to, you two
Civil Affairs Bureau
Right now
You got it
Having second thoughts
You sound a bit jealous, Mr. Fu
I just want to make sure
if the bride has changed her mind
I haven't
From the moment I replaced the groom
I never looked back
Got all your documents
My ID and household register
are in my bag
Very well-prepared
I was preparing for the wrong guy before